- 你是谁 - 卡西迪奥
- Who are you? - Castiel.
- 我意思是 你是什么 - 我是侍奉主的天使
- I mean what are you? - I'm an angel of the lord.
那些复活的长老是66封印之一
The rising of the witnesses is one of the 66 seals.
那些封印被莉莉丝给破坏了
Those seals are being broken by lilith.
最后一道封印被解开
Last one opens and…
路西法就自由了
Lucifer walks free.
- 你开始用你的超能力了吗 - 没有
- So, you been using your, uh, freaky e.s.p. stuff? - No.
好吧 就让它顺其自然吧
Yeah, well, let's keep it that way.
我只是把恶魔从躯体中赶出来
I'm just exorcising demons.
用你的意志
With your mind!
我可以把他们送回地狱
I can send them back to hell.
- 但请从另一个角度看看 - 另一角度
- But try to see the other side here. - The other side?!
我把恶魔从无辜人群中驱除出去
I'm pulling demons out of innocent people.
- 可以用刀啊 - 用刀会杀了受害者
- Use the knife! - The knife kills the victim.
而我能让他们存活下来
What I do, most of them survive!
你应该对我放尊重点
You should show me some respect.
我能拉你出地狱
I dragged you out of hell.
大可以把你扔回去
I can throw you back in.
商店情况怎样
How was the store?
一片狂乱
Oh, madness.
是吗
Yeah?
镇上所有人都在采购
Everyone in town was stocking up.
该买的都买了吗
Did, uh, you get enough?
为了这些我可和诺玛·布莱克推搡了好久
I had to arm-wrestle norma bleaker for these.
亲爱的 她可74岁了
Honey, she's 74.
可比看上去健壮的多了
And a lot stronger than she looks.
记得去年吗 我们6点30就吃完了
Remember last year? we ran out at 6:30.
就一颗 喂喂喂
It's just one piece. unh-unh-unh-unh.
在万圣节后
You can have as much as you want…
你想吃多少就吃多少
After halloween.
不行
No.
看啊谁该洗洗了
Oh, who needs a bath?
去洗澡喽
Oh, there we go!
你来吗
You coming?
我一分钟后上来
I'll, uh, I'll be up in a minute.
好吧
Okay.
卢克 怎么这么久啊
Luke, what's taking you so long?
天那
Oh, my god.
上帝啊
Oh, my god!
[邪恶力量 第4季第7集]
他们找到了多少刀片
Now, how many razor blades did they find?
两片在地上 一片在他胃里 还有片卡在他喉咙里
Two on the floor, one in his stomach, and one was stuck in his throat.
他吞了四片下去
He swallowed four of them.
这怎么可能呢
How is that even possible?
糖果可不会跑到烤箱里去
The candy was never in the oven.
一切都得检查 华莱士夫人
We just have to be thorough, mrs. wallace.
警察在其余糖果里有发现刀片吗
Did the police find any razors in the rest of the candy?
没有
No.
我是说我不知道 我不这么觉得
I mean, i don't know. I don't think so.
我只是
I just…
无法相信这一切
I can't believe it.
你在都市传说上看过这事 但这真有其事吗
You hear urban legends about this stuff, but it actually happens?
超乎你的想象
More than you might imagine.
华莱士夫人 卢克有什么仇家吗
Mrs. wallace, did luke have any enemies?
仇家
Enemies?
对他有过恨意的人
Anyone who might have held a grudge against him?
你想说什么呀
What do you mean?
同事
Co-workers.
邻居
Neighbors.
也许是女人
Maybe a woman.
你是在暗示婚外情吗
Are you suggesting an affair?
有这可能吗
Is it possible?
绝不可能
No!
- 不可能 卢克绝不会 - 我很抱歉
- No, luke would nev… - I'm very sorry.
我们不得不考虑所有的可能性
We just have to consider all possibilities.
如果有人想杀了我丈夫
If someone wanted to kill my husband,
就会想出比在一颗他可能吃的糖果里放刀片
Don't you think they'd find a better way.
更行得通的方法
Than a razor in a piece of candy he might eat?
不是吧
Really?
那家伙可吞下所有刀片哦
After that guy choked down all those razor blades?
万圣节呢 伙计
It's halloween, man.
是啊
Yeah.
对于我们而言 每天都是万圣节
For us, every day is halloween.
别装的那么镇定
Don't be a downer.
有什么发现
Anything interesting?
这次是搜查巫婆 这点可以肯定
Well, we're on a witch-hunt, that's for sure.
但这不是你典型的魔法袋
But this isn't your typical hex bag.
不是吗
Hmm. no?
黄连 已经绝种200年的草药
Goldthread … an herb that's been extinct for 200 years.
这个是凯尔特货币 我不是说那些仿造币
And this is celtic, and I don't mean some new age knock-off.
看上去那么的精致 像600年前那么真
Looks like the real deal … like 600-years-old real.
还有
And, uh…
那个是新生儿的烧焦的掌骨
That is the charred metacarpal bone of a newborn baby.
真恶心
Oh, gross.
放轻松 伙计
Relax, man.
这看起来至少有100年历史
It's, like, at least 100 years old.
好吧 这么弄可以让魔咒的效果更好吗
Oh, right, like that makes it better?
巫婆 伙计 他们真是怪异变态
Witches, man. they're so freaking skeevy.
就是说
Yeah.
弄个袋子把这些放一块产生的魔力很大吧
Well, it takes a pretty powerful one to put a bag like this together.
肯定比以前碰到的要厉害的多 这点可以肯定
More juice than we've ever dealt with before, that's for sure.
你呢 在受害者身上有找到什么吗
What about you … find anything on the victim?
卢克·华莱士 非常平凡
This luke wallace … he was so vanilla that he made vanilla seem spicy.
我不知道为何有人会想要他死
I can't find any reason why somebody would want this guy dead.
这可是聚会挑逗哦
This party blows.
我们该去钓个男人
We should just go t.p. somebody.
好啊 贾斯汀
Uh, hey, justin.
嗨
Yo.
你闯进酒吧了吗
You break into the booze yet?
上了三把锁呢
Uh, it's triple-locked.
你们明晚会去陵墓晚会吗
So, you guys going to the mausoleum party tomorrow night?
你会去吗
Are you gonna be there?
肯定很激动人心 我都等不及了
It's gonna be rad. I'm gonna get so baked.
肯定比这逊毙了的节日强多了
Well, it's got to be better than this g-rated assfest.
得了吧 也没这么逊吧
Oh, come on, it's not that bad.
那么我们来验证下
Oh, check it out.
好吧 敲打苹果会残废哦
Okay, bobbing for apples is lame.
得了吧 这可是万圣节啊
Oh, come on, it's halloween.
残废
Uh…lame.
我错了
I stand corrected.
好吧 我也想试
Well, i want to try.
她还真能憋气
She can really hold her breath.
珍妮
Jenny?
快来帮我
Help me!
珍妮
Jenny!
救命
Help!
珍妮
Jenny!
珍妮 发生什么了
Jenny! what is happening?
珍妮 加油
Jenny, come on!
珍妮
Jenny!
救命 珍妮
Help! jenny!
上帝啊
Oh, my god.
是的
Yes.
这个妞我来
I got this one.
俩字 祸水
Two words … jail bait.
我绝不会的
I would never.
知道吗 这实在是怪异
You know, it's just so weird.
浴盆里的水 绝不可能是热的
I mean, the water in the tub … it wasn't hot.
我自己也刚体验过
I had just been in there myself.
你朋友认不认识一个叫卢克·华莱士的人
You friend didn't happen to know a man named luke wallace?
FBI探员西格
Agent seger … fbi.
谁是卢克·华莱士
Um, who's luke wallace?
他昨天死了
He died yesterday.
我不认识他
I don't know who that is.
告诉你 两个受害者都没有前科
I'm telling you, both of these vics are squeaky-clean.
没任何理由被这么卑鄙的杀害
There was no reason for wicked-bitch payback.
也许事情并非如此
Maybe 'cause it's not about that.
真有见解
Wow. insightful.
也许女巫并非恨意
Maybe this witch isn't working a grudge.
而是某种诅咒
Maybe they're working a spell.
看看这个
Check this out.
在超过三天内有超过三个血祭
"three blood sacrifices over three days … the last.
在收获的最后一天的午夜
Before midnight on the final day of the final harvest."
根据凯尔特人的日历
Celtic calendar…
收获的最后一天是在10月31号
the final day of the final harvest is october 31st.
- 万圣节 - 对啊
- Halloween? - Exactly.
这就是血祭的真正目的吗
What exactly are the, uh, blood sacrifices for?
如果我没猜错 这个巫婆在召集恶魔
Uh, if I'm right, this witch is summoning a demon.
还有不单单是小鬼 还有死神
And not just any demon … samhain.
我该对他有印象吗
Am I supposed to be impressed?
迪恩 死神是来源于万圣节的恶魔
Dean, samhain is the damn origin of halloween.
那些凯尔特人相信在
The celts believed that.
10月31日是一年之中
october 31st was the one night of the.
在生与死之间的隔膜
Year when the veil was thinnest.
最脆弱的一天
between the living and the dead.
所以这就是死神之夜
And it was samhain's night.
人们带上面具去躲避死神
I mean, masks were put on to hide from him,
留在楼梯上的糖果是来安抚死神
Sweets left on doorsteps to appease him,
刻在南瓜上的脸谱是为了对死神表示崇拜
Faces carved into pumpkins to worship him.
他在几个世纪之前就被驱逐了
He was exorcised centuries ago.
所以死神回了一趟地狱
So even though samhain took a trip downstairs,
这个传统就这样形成了
the tradition stuck.
正是
Exactly.
只是现在 没有了恶魔和厮杀
Only now, instead of demons and blood orgies,
万圣节已经成了小孩子的节日
, halloween is all about kids,
糖果和戏服
Candy, and costumes.
所以有哪个巫婆想召集死神
Okay, so some witch wants to raise samhain.
和让那一晚重演吗
and take back the night?
迪恩 这不是闹着玩的 我是认真的
Dean, this is serious. I am serious.
我们在对抗的是重量级的女魔头
We're talking heavyweight witchcraft.
这样的仪式只能在600年举办一次
This ritual can only be performed every 600 years.
在600年前这样的事情是发生在
And the 600-year marker rolls around…
明天晚上 通常是这样
Tomorrow night. naturally.
我们可以确定就因为一个恶魔
Well, it sure is a lot of.
会有很多人死和毁灭
death and destruction for one demon.
那东西就像一个组织
That's 'cause he likes company.
一旦他被唤醒了 死神就可以自己唤醒自己了
Once he's raised, samhain can do some raising of his own.
唤醒什么 说真的
Raising what, exactly?
黑暗 邪恶之灵还有很多这些东西
Dark, evil crap and lots of it.
他们会跟着他就像吹笛手一样
They follow him around like the friggin' pied piper.
那么我们是在说鬼魂吧 是的
So we're talking ghosts. yeah.
僵尸
Zombies? mm-hmm.
妖精 迪恩
Leprechauns? dean.
那些小鬼头很胆小 手小小的
Those little dudes are scary. small hands.
听着 这个仪式是开始与鬼魂和食尸鬼
Look, it just starts with ghosts and ghouls.
他们会一直都很胆小 可是一旦夜晚结束
This sucker keeps on going, by night's end,
他们就会变成我们见过的最恐怖的东西
We are talking every awful thing we've ever seen,
所有我们要干掉的东西都集中在一个地方
Everything we fight all in one place.
那将回成为屠杀场
It's gonna be a slaughterhouse.
喂
Hey.
怎样了
How's it going?
很棒
Awesome.
是的 我又是再说剃刀小姐了
Yeah, i talked with mrs. razor blade again.
我已经在她家门前干坐了几个小时
I've been sitting out in front of her house for hours,
除了一堆雾之外 我啥也看不到
and I've got a big, steamy pile of nothing.
听着 迪恩 有人在在对那个妖术袋子心怀不轨
Look, dean, someone planted those hex bags,
有些人会进入那两间房子
Someone with access to both houses.
这之间一定有什么联系
There's got to be some connection.
是啊 那么
Yeah, well,
我希望我能快点找到他
I hope we find him soon 'cause I'm.
因为我己经像一个兔崽子一样在抽筋了
Starting to cramp like a … son of a bitch.
别抱怨了
Quit whining.
不是 我是说“兔崽子”
No, sam, I mean "son of a bitch."
怎样
So?
我们那个咬苹果的啦啦队队长
Our apple-bobbing cheerleader?
崔西
Tracy? mm-hmm.
是华莱士家的保姆
The wallaces' babysitter.
她跟我说她从来没有听说过卢克 华莱士
She told me she'd never even heard of luke wallace.
对于一个上百岁的女巫婆来说是一个不错的样子
Interesting look for a centuries-old witch.
是啊
Yeah, well,
如果你都600岁了然后想打扮一下回来
If you were a 600-year-old hag and you could pick any.
难道你不会伪装
Costume to come back in,
成啦啦队队长吗
wouldn't you go for a hot cheerleader?
我会的
I would.
行了 崔西并不像她看起来那么健康
Well, tracy's not as wholesome as she looks.
查了一下
Did some digging.
很显然她跟她其中一个老师
Apparently, she got into a violent altercation.
发生过很严重的争吵
with one of her teachers.
被逐出了学校
Got suspended from school.
想起些什么了吗
Bring back memories?
你啥意思
What do you mean?
在青春期的时候 充满着焦虑
Being a teenager, all that angst.
你以为我说什么
What'd you think I meant?
没啥
Nothing.
那就唤起我一些记忆了
Now, that brings back memories.
伙计 我要一个更大的窑
Dude, i need a bigger kiln.
两位先生想跟我聊聊吗
You gentlemen wanted to talk to me?
哈丁先生
Ah, mr. harding.
叫我唐就好了
Oh, please. don.
好啊 唐
Okay, don.
就连我的学生也叫我唐
Even my students call me don.
我们懂了 唐
Yeah, we get it, don.
我是盖迪特工 他是李特工
Uh, i'm agent geddy. this is agent lee.
我们想问问关于崔西 戴维斯的一些事情
We just had a few questions about, uh, tracy davis.
哦 崔西
Uh, yeah, tracy.
是个聪明的孩子 很有天分
Uh, bright kid, loads of talent.
她被赶出校真是可惜
It's a shame she got suspended.
你们曾经发生过激烈的争吵是吗
You two had a, uh, violent altercation.
是啊 她都发狂了
Yeah, she exploded.
如果当时莫罗校长不是刚好经过的话
Uh, if principal murrow hadn't walked by when he did,
崔西可能就已经把我的眼睛挖出来了
Tracy would have clawed my eyes out.
为什么
Why?
我只是想评论一下她的作品
You know, i was only trying to rap with her about her work.
她就反应过度了
It had gotten inappropriate and disturbing.
比那些家伙的反应更过度吗
More disturbing than … than, uh, those guys?
她在每一页纸上都画上满满的
She would cover page after page.
奇怪诡异的标志
with these bizarre cryptic symbols.
还有一些画
And then there were the drawings.
是对厮杀 血淋淋的场景的细节描绘
… detailed images of killings, gory,
是她的原创
primitive.
她会把她自己也画在里面
She would depict herself in the middle of them,
就像是身临其境
participating.
标志 什么标志
Symbols? what kind of symbols?
是类似这样的吗
Uh, anything like this?
是的 是的 我想这就是其中一个
Yeah. yeah, i think that might have been one of them.
你知道崔西现在在哪吗
You know where tracy is now?
也许在她的公寓
I would imagine her apartment.
- 她的公寓 - 是的
- Her apartment? - Yeah.
据我所知 她搬到那里一个人已经住了差不多一年了
She got here about a year ago alone, as I understood it,
就像是刚放出来的年轻人
As an emancipated teen.
天知道她的父母是怎样的
God only knows what her parents were like.
怎样
So?
我在哪都找不到崔西
Tracy was nowhere I could find.
跟她朋友能问出些什么吗
Any luck with her friends?
今天踩不到狗屎运了
Luck is not our style.
她的朋友也不知道她在哪
Friends don't know where she is.
就像一个骑着扫帚的女巫
It's like the bitch hopped a broom.
她可以在任何时间进行她的第三次血祭
She could be making the third sacrifice any time.
是的 谢啦 萨姆
Yes, thank you, sam.
不给糖我就捣蛋
Trick or treat.
这里是一个汽车旅馆
This is a motel.
那又怎样
So?
我们就没有糖果啊
So we don't have any candy.
不是 我们有很多在…现在没了
No, we have a ton in the, uh … we did, but it's gone.
抱歉咯 小弟弟 我们帮不了你
Sorry, kid, we can't help you.
我要糖
I want candy.
我觉得你吃的已经够多的了
Well, i think you've had enough.
你是谁
Who are you?!
等等 萨姆
Sam, sam, wait!
是卡西迪奥
It's castiel…
那个天使
The angel.
他我就不认识了
Him, i don't know.
你好啊 萨姆
Hello, sam.
天哪
Oh, my god.
嗯 对不起 我不是故意的
Er, uh, i didn't mean to … sorry.
发自内心的
It's an honor.
说真的 久仰大名
Really, i-i've heard a lot about you.
我也是
And i, you.
萨姆.温切斯特 流着恶魔血液的那个男孩
Sam winchester … the boy with the demon blood.
很高兴得知你已经不再练习用意志驱魔了
Glad to hear you've ceased your extracurricular activities.
那就保持这样子吧
Let's keep it that way.
行啊 哥儿们
Yeah, okay, chuckles.
你的朋友是谁
Who's your friend?
山姆海茵复活 … 你阻止它了吗
This raising of samhain … have you stopped it?
为什么 迪恩 你搞清女巫的位置没
Why? dean, have you located the witch?
搞清楚了
Yes, we've located the witch.
女巫死了吗
And is the witch dead?
没有 不过 … 我们知道她是谁了
No, but … we know who it is.
显然 女巫也知道你是谁
Apparently, the witch knows who you are, too.
这玩意儿以前在你屋子的墙里面
This was inside the wall of your room.
如果我们没有发现 你们俩都得完蛋
If we hadn't found it, surely one or both of you would be dead.
你知道女巫现在在哪
Do you know where the witch is now?
我们正在查
We're working on it.
点儿太背了
That's unfortunate.
你关心什么
What do you care?
山姆海茵的复活是66个印记之一
The raising of samhain is one of the 66 seals.
所以这和咱们的哥们路西法有关
So this is about your buddy lucifer.
路西法和咱不是一伙的
Lucifer is no friend of ours.
我就这么一说
It's just an expression.
露西佛不能复活
Lucifer cannot rise.
必须不惜一切代价阻止印记被破坏
The breaking of the seal must be prevented at all costs.
好吧
Okay. great.
你现在在这里 为什么不告诉我们女巫在哪
Well, now that you're here, why don't you tell us where the witch is?
我们会干掉她 然后大家各回各家
We'll gank her, and everybody goes home.
我们不是万事通 这女巫很厉害的
We are not omniscient. this witch is very powerful.
她擅长伪装 特别对我们这些人来说
She's cloaked, even to our methods.
好吧 我们已知道她是谁
Okay, well, we already know who she is.
- 所以我们合作的话 - 就谈到这里吧
- So, if we work together… - Enough of this.
你算老几 我干嘛听你的
Who are you, and why should I care?
这是尤瑞尔
This is uriel.
你们可以叫他
He's what you might call…
专家
A specialist.
啥专家
What kind of a specialist?
你们要干嘛
What are you gonna do?
你们…你们俩马上给我离开这里
You… both of you, you need to leave this town immediately.
为什么
Why?
因为我们要摧毁它
Because we're about to destroy it.
没时间了
We're out of time.
女巫必须要死 封印必须要保证完好
This witch has to die. the seal must be saved.
这里有上千人啊
There are a thousand people here.
1214人
1, 214.
你准备连他们一起干掉
And you're willing to kill them all?
这不是我第一次做这个
This isn't the first time I've…
净化一个城市
Purified a city.
兄弟 我理解这么做很遗憾
Look, i understand this is regrettable.
遗憾
Regrettable?
我们要坚持住
We have to hold the line.
太多封印被破坏了
Too many seals have broken already.
所以就因为你们把封印搞砸了
So you screwed the pooch on some seals,
这个城市就要付出代价
And now this town has to pay the price?
这是选择一千人或者六十亿人的问题
It's the lives of 1, 000 against the lives of 6 billion.
这还有更大的问题
There's a bigger picture here.
好吧
Right…
因为 你们这些人前途无量
'cause, uh, you're bigger-picture kind of guys.
路西法不能复活
Lucifer cannot rise.
路西法如果复活 地狱将被他主宰
He does, and hell rises with him.
这就是你们要冒险的原因
Is that something that you're willing to risk?
我们要在女巫召唤任何妖怪之前组织她
We'll stop this witch before she summons anyone.
你的印记不会破坏 谁都不会死的
Your seal won't be broken, and no one has to die.
我们在和这些鸟人浪费时间
We're wasting time with these mud monkeys.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
但我们有命令在身
But we have our orders.
你们不能这么做 你们是天使
No, you can't do this. you … you're angels.
我是说 你们不希望 你们一点怜悯心都没有吗
I mean, aren't you supposed to … you're supposed to show mercy.
说谁呢
Says who?
我们别无选择
We have no choice.
当然有选择
Of course you have a choice.
我是说 你们从没有质疑过命令对吗
I mean, come on, what, you've never … never questioned a crap order, huh?
你们俩难道是铁石心肠吗
What are you both, just a couple of hammers?
看 就算你不明白 也应该相信这个计划是正义的
Look, even if you can't understand it, have faith the plan is just.
你咋这么说呢
How can you even say that?
因为它来自天堂 是正义的象征
Because it comes from heaven. that makes it just.
你们这么肯定 挺好
It must be nice to be so sure of yourselves.
跟我说说 迪恩
Tell me something, dean.
你父亲给你命令 你们都不是在照做么
When your father gave you an order, didn't you obey?
抱歉孩子们 计划变了
Sorry, boys, it looks like the plans have changed.
你以为你能阻止我们
You think you can stop us?
不是
No.
但如果你们要毁了这个城市
But if you're gonna smite this whole town…
那就把我们一起毁了吧 因为我们不会走的
Then you're gonna have to smite us with it because we are not leaving.
你们不要把自己搅入麻烦
You went to the trouble of busting me out of hell.
我觉得我对天堂的那些家伙是有价值的
I figure I'm worth something to the man upstairs.
你想要牺牲我么
You want to waste me?
继续
Go ahead.
看这个鸟人搞什么
See how he digs that.
我会靠自己把你拖出来的
I will drag you out of here myself.
成啊 但你得先杀了我
Yeah, but you'll have to kill me.
然后我们就回到老问题上了
Then we're back to the same problem.
来吧
I mean, come on.
你就为了一个女巫把全城都毁灭
You're gonna wipe out a whole town for one little witch?
感觉像我要赔偿你什么似的
Sounds to me like you're compensating for something.
我们可以做到
We can do this.
找到那个女巫
We will find that witch.
阻止邪恶的召唤
We will stop the summoning.
卡西迪奥 我不会让这些 … 够了
Castiel, I will not let these … enough.
动作最好快点
I suggest you move quickly.
太空人
Astronaut!
啥
What?
没啥
Nothing.
我以为他们与众不同呢
I thought they'd be different.
谁 天使们
Who, the angels?
嗯
Yeah.
我试着给你解释
Well, i tried to tell you.
我刚刚 … 我以为他们是正义的一方
I just … I mean, i thought they'd be righteous.
好吧 他们是好人
Well, they are righteous.
我是说 这是个问题
I mean, that's kind of the problem.
废话
Of course,
没有比人脑子发热去执行神圣任务
There's nothing more dangerous than some.
更危险的了
A-hole who thinks he's on a holy mission.
但是我认为 这是上帝还是天堂
But, i mean, this is god and heaven?
这就是我一直祈祷的
This is what I've been praying to?
哥们
Look, man,
我理解你相信上帝
I know you're into the whole god thing.
还有基督的那些事情
And jesus on a tortilla and stuff like that.
但是我们不能
But just because there's a couple of bad.
以偏概全
Apples doesn't mean the whole barrel is rotten.
我是说 上帝不喜欢这些坏人 我们都知道
I mean, for all we know, god hates these jerks.
不要放弃我提到的这些
Don't give up on the stuff is all I'm saying.
宝贝露丝是个骗子 棒球游戏还得继续
Babe ruth was a dick, but baseball's still a beautiful game.
好了 你准备好找到女巫了吗
Well, are you gonna figure out a way to find this witch,
或者坐在这里守着老骨头
Or are you just gonna sit there fingering your bone?
你知道什么温度才能把骨骼烧焦 迪恩
You know how much heat it would take to char a bone like this, dean?
不知道
No.
很高
A lot.
比厨房烤箱温度高 起码
I mean, more than a fire or some kitchen oven.
好吧 贝蒂妙厨 啥意思啊
Okay, betty crocker, what does that mean?
让我们停止
It means we make a stop.
所以 崔西用窑来烧骨头
So, tracy used a kiln to char the bone?
什么大人物这是
What's the big deal?
迪恩 魔法袋是在我们和崔西说话后出现在房间里的
Dean, that hex bag turned up in our room not after we talked to tracy…
和那个老师说话完之后
After we talked to the teacher.
我滴神啊
Oh, my god.
小孩子
Those are all from children.
我猜他不是为了狗去救他们
I'm guessing he's not saving them for the dog.
该做决定了
The decision's been made.
那俩鸟人
By a mud monkey.
别这么喊他们
You shouldn't call them that.
他们就是这玩意 会走路的野人而已
Oh, that's what they are … savages, just plumbing on two legs.
你快成老怨妇了
You're close to blasphemy.
我们被派来救他是有原因的
There's a reason we were sent to save him.
他有潜力获得成功
He has potential. he may succeed here.
无论如何
At any rate…
不是我们可以控制的
It's out of our hands.
没这个必要
It doesn't have to be.
你怎么想
And what would you suggest?
我们把迪恩 温彻斯特扔在这儿
That we drag dean winchester out of here,
然后我们把这些无关紧要的针从地图上拔下
Then we blow this insignificant pinprick off the map.
你知道我们真正的指令
You know our true orders.
你打算违抗吗
Are you prepared to disobey?
谢谢 他想要杀了我
Thank you. he was gonna kill me.
这个病态的混蛋
Ugh, that sick son of a bitch.
你们看到他做的这些个事了吗
I mean, did you see what he was doing?
你们有听到他念了吗
Did you hear him…
他的咒语总是那么么粗糙
How sloppy his incantation was?
我兄弟总有那么点傻
My brother always was a little dim.
他想让我做最后的祭品
He was gonna make me the final sacrifice.
他的主意
His idea.
但现在这份荣誉归他了
But now, that honor goes to him.
我们的主人又回来了
Our master has returned.
这份轮班工作需要俩人 你们了解吗
This spellwork's a two-man job, you understand?
所以600年来 我都和这傲慢的混蛋妥协
So for 600 years, I had to deal with that pompous son of a bitch.
计划着 准备着 真是忍无可忍
Planning, preparing … unbearable.
一直以来 我都想撕下他的脸
The whole time, I wanted to rip his face off.
然后
And…
你们用枪搞定了他
…you get him with a gun.
我欢欣雀跃
Oh, i love that.
知道吗 若在过去
You know, back in the day,
这个晚上你该把孩子关在屋内
This was the one night you kept your children inside.
今晚 你们将见识什么才是真正的万圣节
Well, tonight, you'll all see what halloween really is.
你要做什么
What … what are you doing?
听我的就对了
Just follow my lead.
亲爱的
My love.
你老了
You've aged.
这张脸
This face…
我不能骗你
I can't fool you.
你的美丽早已超越时空
Your beauty is beyond time.
贱人
Whore.
那到底是什么鬼东西
What the hell was that?
万圣节传说
Halloween lore.
人们过去都是戴着面具来躲避他的 所以我尽力而为
People used to wear masks to hide from him, so I gave it a shot.
你尽力而为
You gave it a shot?
我们怎样才能找到那杂种
How are we gonna find this mook?
如果是你想在哪复活这些黑暗力量
Where would you go to raise all the dark forces of the night?
公墓
A cemetery.
对极了
Yeah.
这个恶魔法力无边
So, this demon's pretty powerful.
就是说
Yeah.
可能需要用到不同寻常的武器
It might take more than the usual weapons.
萨姆 不可以
Sam, no.
不管怎样都不能用你的魔力
You're not using your psychic whatever.
- 但是 - 想都别想
- But… - Don't even think about it.
- 露比的刀就够了 - 为什么
- Ruby's knife is enough. - Why?
天使是这么说来着
Because the angel said so, for one.
我想你说过他们是一群宗教狂
I thought you said they were a bunch of fanatics.
- 好吧 对于这点他们碰巧说对了 - 我想不通 迪恩
- Well, they happen to be right about this. - I don't know, dean.
看起来他们对的不多
It doesn't seem like they're right about much.
听着 忘了天使 好吗
Look, forget the angels, okay?
你说你自己 这些力量 就像玩火
You said yourself, these powers … it's like playing with fire.
求你了
Please.
伙计 我正参加舞会呢
Dude, I'm tripping balls.
安静下 是警察
Yo, shh. be quiet. it's the cops.
哈丁先生
Mr. harding?
我说 唐
I mean…don?
唐 你把我们锁里面了
Uh, don, you, uh … you locked us in.
- 帮帮他们 - 伙计 你不要一个人乱来
- Help them. - Dude, you're not going off alone.
快点
Do it.
退后 退后
Stand back! stand back!
快点 快点 快点
Come on, come on, come on!
快跑
Move!
准备好了 来吧 恶臭先生们
Bring it on, stinky.
好吧
Yeah.
恶魔光线炮
That demon-ray-gun stuff…
对我没用
Doesn't work on me.
僵尸与鬼魂的亲密接触
Zombie-ghost orgy, huh?
对 就是那样
Well, that's it.
我去烧了所有人
I'm torching everybody.
明天是11月2号
Tomorrow is november 2nd.
是你的一个纪念日对吧
That's an anniversary for you, right?
你来这儿做什么
What are you doing here?
22年前的明天亚撒色杀了你妈妈
It's the day azazel killed your mother and, 22 years later,
22年后杀了你女友
Your girlfriend, too.
很难忍受吧 但你却厚着脸皮用了他给你的能量
It must be difficult to bear, yet you brazenly use the power he gave you,
他那亵渎神灵的血液在你的血管里流动着
His profane blood pumping through your veins.
你说什么
Excuse me?
告诉过你别再用魔力了
You were told not to use your abilities.
我该怎么做
What was I supposed to do?
那个恶魔会杀了我和我哥哥以及所有人
That demon would have killed me and my brother and everyone.
告诉过你别用
You were told not to.
- 如果山姆海茵在这个镇被释放 - 现在二次警告
- If samhain had gotten loose in this town… - Been warned twice now.
知道吗 我哥哥对你的看法是对的
You know, my brother was right about you.
你真鸡巴
You are dicks.
你存活的唯一理由 萨姆·温彻斯特
The only reason you're still alive, sam winchester,
是因为你还有用
Is because you've been useful.
这一刻将成为历史
The moment that ceases to be true,
下一秒你就功不抵过了
The second you become more trouble then you're worth,
再多说一个字 一个字 我就把你变成尘土
One word … one … and I will turn you to dust.
至于你哥哥
As for your brother,
告诉他该收收他的锐气了
Tell him that maybe he should climb off that high horse of his.
问问迪恩
Ask dean…
他在地狱的记忆
What he remembers from hell.
我来猜猜
Let me guess.
你来这儿是想说我早告诉过你
You're here for the "i told you so."
不是
No.
好极了 因为我实在不感兴趣
Well, good, 'cause I'm really not that interested.
我不是来这儿审判你的 迪恩
I am not here to judge you, dean.
那为什么你在这儿
Then why are you here?
- 我们的指示 对 知道吗
- Our orders… - Yeah, you know.
我受够了你们的指示
I've had about enough of these orders of yours.
我们的指示
Our orders…
不是停止召唤山姆海茵
Were not to stop the summoning of samhain.
他们依照你对我们的指示来做事
They were to do whatever you told us to do.
你们的指示来自于我的指示
Your orders were to follow my orders?
这是个测试
It was a test…
看看你在战争条件下
To see how you would perform under…
怎样表现 你可以这么说
Battlefield conditions, you might say.
这是个巫婆
It was a witch…
而不是所谓的战争测试
Not the tet offensive.
那么我不合格吗
So, i, uh, failed your test, huh?
我知道了
I get it.
但你知道吗
But you know what?
如果你挥动下魔棒 去除了那段魔法时光
If you were to waive that … that magic time-traveling wand of.
我们就得重新再来遍 我要打同一个电话
Yours and we had to do it all over again, I'd make the same call…
因为我不知道当这些封印被打破后会发生什么
'cause, see, I don't know what's gonna happen when these seals are broken.
见鬼 我都不知道明天会发生什么
Hell, i don't know what's gonna happen tomorrow.
但我知道这个地方 这些孩子 这种摇摆
But what I do know is is that this here … these kids, the swings,
这些树 所有的这些正因为我弟弟和我才能在这儿的
The trees, all of it … is still here because of my brother and me.
你误解我了 迪恩
You misunderstand me, dean.
我并非你所想
I'm not like you think.
我祈祷你会选择拯救这个镇
I was praying that you would choose to save the town.
你真的是这样吗
You were?
这些人 他们都是上帝创造的
These people … they're all my father's creations.
他们都是艺术品
They're works of art.
还有
And yet…
尽管你们制止了山姆海茵 封印被打破
Even though you stopped samhain, the seal was broken,
对于地球上所有生物而言我们离地狱又近了一步
And we are one step closer to hell on earth for all creation.
不只是说说而已 迪恩
And that's not an expression, dean.
这是事实
It's literal.
你们人类应该
You of all people should…
接受这个事实
Appreciate what that means.
我会告诉你一些事你发誓不会告诉别人
I'll tell you something if you promise not to tell another soul.
好的
Okay.
我不是
I'm not, uh…
一个坚定不移的人 就如你所说
A hammer, as you say.
我也会有疑问
I have questions.
我
I…
我也有过怀疑
I have doubts.
我不知道孰对孰错
I don't know what is right and what is wrong anymore…
也无法判定你是否失败或成功
And whether you passed or failed here.
但在未来的几个月里 你会下定决心的
But in the coming months, you will he more decisions to make.
我并不羡慕你所担负的重任 迪恩
I don't envy the weight that's on your shoulders, dean.
我真的不羡慕
I truly don't.